Guide to the Danbury, Town of Records 1892-1969 DRG 1 DRG.1
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I: Financial Records, 27317
  - Annual Reports, 1893-1964/Acc #191-1976, 27322
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1939; 27355 (Box 5.1, Folder 42)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1940; 27354 (Box 5.1, Folder 43)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1941; 27353 (Box 5.1, Folder 44)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1942; 27352 (Box 5.1, Folder 45)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1943; 27351 (Box 5.1, Folder 46)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1944; 27350 (Box 5.1, Folder 47)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1950; 27349 (Box 5.1, Folder 48)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1951; 27348 (Box 5.1, Folder 49)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1952; 27347 (Box 5.1, Folder 50)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury (2c), 1953; 27346 (Box 5.1, Folder 51)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1954; 27345 (Box 5.1, Folder 52)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1955; 27344 (Box 5.1, Folder 53)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1956; 27343 (Box 5.1, Folder 54)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1957; 27342 (Box 5.1, Folder 55)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1959; 27341 (Box 5.1, Folder 56)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1961; 27340 (Box 5.1, Folder 57)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1962; 27339 (Box 5.1, Folder 58)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1963; 27338 (Box 5.1, Folder 59)
    - Annual Report of the Board of Selectmen of the Town of Danbury, 1964; 27337 (Box 5.1, Folder 60)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1923; 27336 (Box 5.2, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1929-1933; 27335 (Box 5.2, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1924; 27334 (Box 5.2, Folder 3-4)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1925; 27333 (Box 5.2, Folder 5-6)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1926; 27332 (Box 5.2, Folder 7-8)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1927; 27331 (Box 5.2, Folder 9-10)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1928; 27330 (Box 5.2, Folder 11-13)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1929; 27329 (Box 5.2, Folder 14-16)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1930; 27328 (Box 5.2, Folder 17-20)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1931; 27327 (Box 5.2, Folder 21-24)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1932; 27326 (Box 5.2, Folder 25-28)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1933; 27325 (Box 5.2, Folder 29-33)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1934; 27324 (Box 5.2, Folder 34-38)
    - Annual Reports (Corporations), 1935; 27323 (Box 5.2, Folder 39-42)
  - Town of Danbury Auditor's Reports, 27320
    - Auditor's Reports, 1939-1943; 27321 (Box 5.3, Folder 1-17)
  - Town of Danbury Tax Receipts, 27318
    - Danbury Tax Receipt Microfilms, 1946-1965; 27319 (Box 5.4, Item 1-98)
      Materials on 16mm microfilm.
- Series II: School Board, 27311
  - School Board Committee Appropriations and Expenditures, 1904-1910, 27315
    - School Board Committee appropriations and expenditures, 1904-1910; 27316 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - School Board Meeting Minutes, 1892-1911/Acc #174-1976, 27312
    - Minutes of School Board Meetings, 1892-1908; 27314 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of School Board Meetings, 1908-1911; 27313 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series III: Town Clerk/Acc #208-1976, 27241
  Partially processed
  - Miscellaneous, 27293
    - Administrator's Deeds, 1917-1930; 27310 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Affidavit of Honora Reidy, 1934; 27309 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Agreements (Release of Agreement), 1928-1945; 27308 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Appointment of Conservator, 1905-1910; 27307 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Assignment of Future Earnings, 1932-1936; 27306 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Assignment of Mortgage, 1928-1952; 27305 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Assignment of Wages, 1930-1936; 27304 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Bond for Deed, 1928-1950; 27303 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of Foreclosure, 1931; 27302 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Certificate of Name Change, 1934-1938; 27301 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1926-1935; 27300 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Certificate of Real Estate (deceased), 1929-1941; 27299 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Certificate of Title, 1933-1935; 27298 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Committee Deed, 1932; 27297 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Contract for Property, 1929; 27296 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Contract of Sale, 1930; 27295 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Distribution Certificate, 1929; 27294 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Voting Records, 1908-1949/Acc #185-1976, 27284
    - Appointments & Oath of Office, 1912-1947; 27292 (Box 8.1, Folder 1-4)
    - Election Results, 1912-1946; 27291 (Box 8.1, Folder 5-10)
    - Elector's Meeting, 1908-1942; 27290 (Box 8.1, Folder 11)
    - Machine Tallies & Receipts for Keys, 1912-1949; 27289 (Box 8.1, Folder 12-20)
    - New Voters, 1923-1949; 27288 (Box 8.2, Folder 21-23)
    - Proposed Amendments, 1911-1947; 27287 (Box 8.2, Folder 24)
    - Qualified Jurors, 1919-1939; 27286 (Box 8.2, Folder 25)
    - Qualified Justices of the Peace, 1924-1947; 27285 (Box 8.2, Folder 26)
    - Danbury Voter Lists, 1960-1961 (OS Folder 3.1)
      General
      Lists of Democratic and Republican men and women, mostly in the first ward.
  - Old Age Assistance Tax Enrollment, 27281
    - Old Age Assistance Tax Enrollment Cards - unsorted cards, 1939-1944; 27283 (Box 8.3)
      This box is comprised of cards that were "uncollated" when processed. Cards contain: name, residence, place and date of birth, occupation, employer, land owner status, voter status, reason for Abatement/Exemption and date of enrollment.
    - Old Age Assistance Tax Enrollment - sorted cards, 1939-1944; 27282 (Box 8.4)
      This box is comprised of cards that were "collated" when processed. Cards are still bound in rubber bands by street address. Cards contain: name, residence, place and date of birth, occupation, employer, land owner status, voter status, reason for Abatement/Exemption and date of enrollment.
  - Danbury Land Office Records, 27242
    - Board of Finance Appropriations, 1956; 27280 (Box 8.5, Folder 1)
    - Certificates of Attachment, Jan 1909-May 1909; 27279 (Box 8.5, Folder 2)
    - Certificates of Attachment, Jun 1909; 27278 (Box 8.5, Folder 3)
    - Certificates of Attachment, Jun 1909; 27277 (Box 8.5, Folder 4)
    - Certificates of Attachment, Jul 1909-Dec 1909; 27276 (Box 8.5, Folder 5)
    - Certificates of Attachment, Jan 1910-Jun 1910; 27275 (Box 8.5, Folder 6)
    - Certificates of Attachment, Jul 1910-Dec 1910; 27274 (Box 8.5, Folder 7)
    - Certificates of Attachment, 1920-1936; 27273 (Box 8.5, Folder 8)
    - City of Danbury - Hartford Accident and Indemnity Insurance, 1935; 27272 (Box 8.5, Folder 9)
    - City of Danbury - Liens, 1893-1895; 27271 (Box 8.5, Folder 10)
    - City of Danbury - Tax Liens, 1936; 27270 (Box 8.5, Folder 11)
    - Conciatore vs. Telford - Memorandum on behalf of landlords, 1950; 27269 (Box 8.5, Folder 12)
    - Judgement Liens, 1929, 1935; 27268 (Box 8.5, Folder 13)
    - Leases, 1910-1935; 27267 (Box 8.5, Folder 13.1)
    - Merchant's Liens, 1930-1938; 27266 (Box 8.5, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Land Records, 1898-1946; 27265 (Box 8.5, Folder 15)
    - Mortgage Deeds, 1928-1947; 27264 (Box 8.5, Folder 16)
    - Notice of Lis Pendens, 1927-1932; 27263 (Box 8.5, Folder 17)
    - Notice of Lis Pendens, 1932-1937; 27262 (Box 8.5, Folder 18)
    - Plaintiff's and Defendant's Bills of Costs, 1905-1911; 27261 (Box 8.5, Folder 19)
    - Power of Attorney, 1929, 1934-1944; 27260 (Box 8.5, Folder 20)
    - Probate - Estate of Martin Fuchs, 1929; 27259 (Box 8.5, Folder 21)
    - Quit Claim Deeds, 1909-1931; 27258 (Box 8.5, Folder 22)
    - Quit Claim Deeds, 1931-1934; 27257 (Box 8.5, Folder 23)
    - Quit Claim Deeds, 1934-1946; 27256 (Box 8.5, Folder 24)
    - Release of Judgement Liens, 1934-1937; 27255 (Box 8.5, Folder 25)
    - Release of Lease, 1929; 27254 (Box 8.5, Folder 26)
    - Release of Trust Deeds, 1930; 27253 (Box 8.5, Folder 27)
    - Releases of Attachment, 1907, 1928-1933; 27252 (Box 8.5, Folder 28)
    - Releases of Attachment, 1928-1938; 27251 (Box 8.5, Folder 29)
    - Selectmen approval of Highway Plan - blue print, 1927; 27250 (Box 8.5, Folder 30)
    - Tax Lien Releases, 1936-1937; 27249 (Box 8.5, Folder 31)
    - Tax Lien Releases, 1943; 27248 (Box 8.5, Folder 32)
    - Town of Danbury - Real Estate Taxes, 1931; 27247 (Box 8.5, Folder 33)
    - Town of Danbury - Tax Liens, 1935; 27246 (Box 8.5, Folder 34)
    - Town of Danbury - Tax Liens, 1936; 27245 (Box 8.5, Folder 35)
    - Town of Danbury - Tax Liens, 1937; 27244 (Box 8.5, Folder 36)
    - Zoning Regulations, 1945-1965; 27243 (Box 8.5, Folder 37)
- Series IV: Town Counsel, 27169
  - Real Estate-Closed, 1912-1960; 27240 (Box 9, Folder 1-6)
  - Legal Opinions, 1920-1965; 27239 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1937; 27238 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Relief Commission-Commodity Distribution, undated; 27237 (Box OS 1)
  - Work Relief, 1940-1941; 27236 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Danbury Airport, 1940-1946; 27235 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Brainard Field Map, Hartford, Conn., 1940; 27234 (Box OS 1)
  - Town of Danbury vs. William R. Burke, 1942; 27233 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Town Meeting, 1944-1945; 27232 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Town of Danbury vs. Dominic Generalli, 1945; 27231 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Housing Bonds, 1946-1948; 27230 (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
  - The Daily Bond Buyer, December 12, 1947; 27229 (Box OS 1)
  - Park Avenue School Bonds, 1946-1950; 27228 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The Daily Bond Buyer, June 8, 15, 17, 1950, 27227 (Box OS 1)
  - Conn-Air, Inc., 1946-1947; 27226 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Aviation Commission, 1946-1947; 27225 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Danbury Airport Bond Issue, 1946-1948; 27224 (Box 9, Folder 23-25)
  - Permits, 1947-1948; 27223 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Beaver Brook School Bonds, 1948-1949; 27222 (Box 9, Folder 27-29)
  - Town Counsel, Miscellaneous, 1948-1949; 27221 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Park Avenue School Bond Issue, 1949; 27220 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Housing Authority, 1949-1960; 27219 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Roberts Avenue School Bond Issue, 1949-1951; 27218 (Box 9, Folder 33-36)
  - Park Avenue School/ Bond Issue/ Certificate Form, 1950; 27217 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - City of Danbury vs. The Danbury Professional Building, Inc., 1950; 27216 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Town Meeting, December 1950, 27215 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Teachers College School--Roberts Avenue Property, 1950-1951; 27214 (Box 9, Folder 40-41)
  - Blueprint: Proposed site for Practice Elementary School, 1950; 27213 (Folder OS Folder 3.1, Item 1)
  - Town Counsel/Budgets, 1950-1951; 27212 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Town Meetings, 1950-1951; 27211 (Box 9, Folder 43-45)
  - Algonquin Gas Transmission Company, Road Crossings, 1951-1952; 27210 (Box 9, Folder 46-48)
  - Blueprint: 26" Main Line New York (Sept. 1951) Revised, October 18, 1951, 27209 (Folder OS Folder 3.1, Item 3a, 3b)
  - Blueprint: 26" Main Line, Connecticut (Aug. 1951), 27208 (Folder OS Folder 3.1, Item 4a-4c)
  - Map: Town Roads in Danbury (Jan.1951), 27207 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item *)
  - Blueprints: Proposed 26 inch Natural Gas Pipeline Under:a. Exhibit G: Ridgewood Street & State Hwy. No. 37Ab. Exhibit I: Berkshire Drivec. Exhibit K: Circle Drive, undated; 27206 (Folder OS Folder 4.1)
  - Algonquin Gas Transmission Company, Hayestown School Property, 1952; 27205 (Box 9, Folder 49-50)
  - Town Meetings, 1952-1953; 27204 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Hayestown School Bonds, 1952-1953; 27203 (Box 9, Folder 52-55)
  - Bids/Calls/School Property, 1952-1954; 27202 (Box 9, Folder 56-57)
  - Town Meeting, June 15, 1953; 27201 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Hayestown Avenue School Funds (Investment), 1953; 27200 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Hayestown Avenue School Bond Issues, 1953; 27199 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Tax Assessor's Office, 1953-1954; 27198 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Danbury Airport, 1953-1955; 27197 (Box 9, Folder 62-63)
  - Town of Danbury vs. Blodget, 1954; 27196 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - South Street School and Park Avenue School Addition Bonds, 1954; 27195 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Tax Appeals, 1954-1956; 27194 (Box 10, Folder 66-67)
  - Tax Appeal Cases Settled, 1955; 27193 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Mill Ridge Area School Bonds, 1955; 27192 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Town Meeting, March 29, 1955; 27191 (Box 10, Folder 70-71)
  - Connecticut Development Credit Corporation, 1955; 27190 (Folder OS Folder 3.1, Item 2)
  - Proposed property lines, April 20, 1955, 27189 (Folder OS Folder 3.1, Item 4)
  - Town Meeting, Raffles & Bazaars, 1955-1956; 27188 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Housing Unit Foreclosures, 1955-1957; 27187 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Charles A. Hallock, Judge, 1955-1961; 27186 (Box 10, Folder 74-78)
  - Mill Ridge Area School Bonds, 1956-1957; 27185 (Box 10, Folder 79-80)
  - Danbury Highway Construction Bonds, 1957; 27184 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Fairfield, Connecticut, 1957-1960; 27183 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Representative Town Meeting, 1957-1960; 27182 (Box 11, Folder 83-87)
  - Road Petitions, 1957-1964; 27181 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Map: Great Meadow Road, undated; 27180 (Box OS 1)
  - Town Meeting, August 28, 1958; 27179 (Box 11, Folder 89-90)
  - Blueprint: Miry Brook Volunteer Fire Co., Inc., 1950; 27178 (Box OS 1)
  - Town of Danbury/Zoning Board vs. Charlie Ward, et al, 1959; 27177 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Danbury Bridge Bonds, 1960; 27176 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Town of Danbury vs. Inez M. Hyatt, 1960-1961; 27175 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Lawrence Duplisea vs. Town of Danbury, 1960-1962; 27174 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Danbury School Bond Issue, 1961; 27173 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - School Bond Issue, 1961; 27172 (Box 11, Folder 96-99)
  - Town of Danbury vs. Barry III, Klein and Morris J. Feinson d/b/aThe Aspen Company, 1962-1963; 27171 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Map: Portion of property to be acquired by the Town of Danbury, 1961; 27170 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
- Series V: Registered Physicians, 1893-1937/Acc #133-1976, 27166
  Contents include names, age, birthplace, residence, college attended, etc. There are also a few loose registration certificates.
  - One ledger, 1893-1937; 27168 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Loose Registration Certificates, 1908-1937; 27167 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Selectmen, Board of 1914-1960/DG179 & DG 209, 26930
  - First Selectman Records, 27133
    - Bids, 1950-1958; 27165 (Box 13.1, Folder 1)
      Bids for Civil Defense and bridge construction.
    - Board of Finance, Minutes of Special Meetings, 1953-1956; 27164 (Box 13.1, Folder 2)
    - Board of Finance, Minutes of Meetings, 1954-1955, 2001, undated; 27163 (Box 13.1, Folder 3)
    - Civil Defense, 1953-1966; 27162 (Box 13.1, Folder 4-5)
      Correspondence, The Family Fallout Shelter, Operation Danbury April 25 and 26, 1953, and Civil Defense Operational Survival Plan.
    - Complaints, 1951-1959; 27161 (Box 13.1, Folder 6)
    - Complaints, Dog Pound, 1958; 27160 (Box 13.1, Folder 7)
    - Consolidation of Town & City of Danbury, 1949-1961; 27159 (Box 13.1, Folder 8)
      Includes extension of city limits.
    - Correspondence, Misc., 1947-1959; 27158 (Box 13.1, Folder 9)
    - Danbury Library, 1950-1954; 27157 (Box 13.1, Folder 10)
      Annual reports.
    - Danbury Power & Transportation Co., 1954; 27156 (Box 13.1, Folder 11)
      Correspondence.
    - Department of Education, 1950-1956; 27155 (Box 13.1, Folder 12)
      Correspondence and minutes of the School Building Committee.
    - Dog Pound, 1953-1958; 27154 (Box 13.1, Folder 13)
    - Electric Code, undated; 27153 (Box 13.1, Folder 14)
    - Flood Aid, August 19, 1955, 27152 (Box 13.1, Folder 15)
    - Health, 1949-1962; 27151 (Box 13.1, Folder 16-19)
      Correspondence regarding health issues, i.e., sewage disposal, contamination of water supply, T.B. cases, etc.
    - Hot Lunch Program, 1936-1959; 27150 (Box 13.1, Folder 20-21)
      Correspondence, forms, Training Course for Relief Workers, Surplus commodity bulletins, WPA lunch program.
    - Insurance, 1951-1964, undated; 27149 (Box 13.1, Folder 22)
    - Ludlow Valve Company, 1934-1935; 27148 (Box 13.1, Folder 23)
      1934 project for sewers, drains and treatment plant.
    - Mill Ridge School, 1949-1957; 27147 (Box 13.1, Folder 24)
      Minutes of Danbury School Building Committee and Survey of School Building Needs by the Conn. State Dept. of Education.
    - Park Avenue School, 1950-1963; 27146 (Box 13.1, Folder 25)
      Correspondence, minutes of School Building Committee, and right
    - Petitions, 1951-1959; 27145 (Box 13.1, Folder 26)
    - Planning Commission, 1963; 27144 (Box 13.1, Folder 27)
      Public Acts and Supplements.
    - Roberts Avenue School, 1951-1954; 27143 (Box 13.1, Folder 28)
      School Building Committee minutes and correspondence.
    - Storm Damage (Floods) October 15, 1955, 1955-1956; 27142 (Box 13.1, Folder 29)
      Correspondence and receipts.
    - State Tax Office, 1952; 27141 (Box 13.1, Folder 30)
    - State Traffic Commission, 1950-1956; 27140 (Box 13.1, Folder 31)
    - Tax Office, 1950-1956; 27139 (Box 13.1, Folder 32)
      Tax collection records and correspondence.
    - Town Housing Authority, 1949-1955; 27138 (Box 13.1, Folder 33)
    - Town Welfare Department, 1949-1951; 27137 (Box 13.1, Folder 34)
      Monies spent on direct relief.
    - Unfinished Business, 1950-1957; 27136 (Box 13.1, Folder 35)
      Correspondence covering a multitude of subjects.
    - Union Activities, 1956-1957; 27135 (Box 13.1, Folder 36)
      Agreement between Town and AFSCME/AFL-CIO members.
    - Vocational School, 1951-1955; 27134 (Box 13.1, Folder 37)
      Correspondence and minutes of School Building Committee.
  - Selectmen Records, 1920-1955, 26931
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1914-1942; 27132 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
    - Accounts Receivable, 1943-1959; 27131 (Box 13, Folder 4-9)
    - A - Misc., 1931-1956; 27130 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Advertising Literature, 1925-1936; 27129 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Aetna Casualty & Surety Company, 1933-1946; 27128 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - A-L Misc., 1953-1956; 27127 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Almshouse Reports, 1930-1948; 27126 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
    - A-R Misc., 1931-1960; 27125 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Assessor's Office, 1933-1959; 27124 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - AT-AV Misc., 1934-1952; 27123 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Atlantic Refining Company, 1937-1943; 27122 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Automatic Voting Machine Corporation, 1931-1949; 27121 (Box 13, Folder 20-21)
    - B-BA Misc., 1930-1956; 27120 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
    - BE-BI Misc., 1931-1955; 27119 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Bids and Notices, 1925-1930; 27118 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Bids and Notices, 1931-1933; 27117 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Bids and Notices, 1934-1935; 27116 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Bids and Notices, 1936; 27115 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Bids and Notices, 1937; 27114 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Bids and Quotations, 1946-1949; 27113 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Bids and Quotations, 1950-1951; 27112 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Bids and Quotations, 1952-1953; 27111 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Bids and Quotations, 1954; 27110 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Bids and Quotations, 1955; 27109 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Bids and Quotations, 1956; 27108 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Bingo-Petitions, 1939-1940; 27107 (Box 13, Folder 36-38)
    - Bingo Permits, 1939-1950; 27106 (Box 13, Folder 39-41)
    - BL - BRI Misc., 1932-1941; 27105 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - BO and Board of Education, 1933-1952; 27104 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Board of Finance-Clerk, 1937-1938; 27103 (Box 13, Folder 44-45)
    - BRI - BUC Misc., 1931-1959; 27102 (Box 13, Folder 46-47)
    - BUR-BY, 1931-1960; 27101 (Box 13, Folder 48-49)
    - C - CA Misc., 1930-1953; 27100 (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
    - CE - CH Misc., 1931-1946; 27099 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Citizens Food & Fuel Conservation Program, 1947-1948; 27098 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - CL Misc., 1931-1950; 27097 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - CO Misc., 1918-1959; 27096 (Box 13, Folder 55-58)
    - Dog Damage, 1914-1949; 27095 (Box 13, Folder 59-62)
    - Commissioner of Domestic Animals, 1950-1958; 27094 (Box 14, Folder 63-67)
    - Compensation Commissioner, 1913-1958; 27093 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Complaints, 1921-1955; 27092 (Box 14, Folder 69-70)
    - Connecticut War Council, 1942-1943; 27091 (Box 14, Folder 70a)
    - Contractor's Supply Company, Inc., 1936-1952; 27090 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - CR-CU Misc., 1932-1947; 27089 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - DA Misc., 1922-1956; 27088 (Box 14, Folder 73-78)
    - Danbury & Bethel Gas Electric Light Company, 1933-1950; 27087 (Box 14, Folder 79-81)
    - Danbury Airport, 1927-1957; 27086 (Box 14, Folder 82-91)
    - Danbury Airport, Danbury Municipal Airport, Exhibit A, 6/9/55 Blueprints: Danbury Municipal Airport Plot Plan 12/20/41, 1941-1955; 27085 (Folder OS Folder 5.1, Item 2)
    - Department of Education, Public Schools, 1923-1947; 27083 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Danbury Airport, Blueprints: Continental, Inc. One Story Shop/Office, 1945; 27084 (Folder OS Folder 2.1, Item 1-9)
    - DE Misc., 1926-1956; 27082 (Box 14, Folder 93-94)
    - Diebold, Inc., 1932-1948; 27081 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Dolan Contracting Company, 1928-1946; 27080 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - Draft Board Documents, 1940-1944; 27079 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - DU Misc., 1931-1960; 27078 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - Dyer Sales & Machinery Company, 1931-1940; 27077 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - E Misc., 1940-1949; 27076 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - Emergency Relief, 1929-1937; 27075 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - FA Misc., 1931-1956; 27074 (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - FE Misc., 1931-1948; 27073 (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - Fence Views and Property Lines, 1921-1952; 27071 (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - FI-FO Misc., 1931-1958; 27070 (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - Foreclosures & Bids on Properties, 1936-1956; 27069 (Box 14, Folder 106-108)
    - FR-FZ Misc., 1931-1956; 27068 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Form Letters, 1931-1936; 27067 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Fuel Oil Letters, 1941-1948; 27066 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - GA Misc., 1931-1950; 27065 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, 1946-1956; 27064 (Box 14, Folder 113-119)
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, 1946-1956; 27063 (Box 15, Folder 120-123)
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, Blueprint: The American Oil Company, Sugar Hollow Road (U.S. #7) Plot Plan. August 16, 1955; 27062 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 1)
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, Blueprint: The American Oil Company, Sugar Hollow Road (U.S. #7) Plot Plan. February 26, 1954; 27061 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 2)
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, Blueprint: Property of Arthur Bramley. May 12, 1954; 27060 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 3)
    - Drawing: Proposed box culvert at rear entrance F.C.I., East Pembroke Rd. Danbury, Conn., 1948; 27072 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 4)
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, Petition: Residence on Golden Hill and immediate district of Beckerle Street, opposition to Novella's junkyard. February 11, 1950; 27059 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 5)